<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>P128 — tiny reviews of tiny games</title>
    <atom:link href="p128.review/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <link>p128.review</link>
    <description>tiny reviews of tiny games</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 10:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
    <generator>Wintersmith - https://github.com/jnordberg/wintersmith</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>MAZE DOG</title>
      <link>p128.review/articles/maze-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 10:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">p128.review/articles/maze-dog/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FIND THE CHICKS! DIG FOR SNACKS! ANNOY THE DUCKS! NAVIGATE THE MAZE! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MAZE DOG&lt;/em&gt; is a cute little adventure game for 1 player, sporting a seriously rad theme tune and a simple yet fun aesthetic! You go from screen to screen controlling a cute little puppy. You need to find 8 chickens that has run away from their home and theres’ 8 “snacks” hidden throughout the game for completionists. Going from screen to screen can be a little dull sometimes, but finding a chick does feel rewarding. Plus there are a bunch of little details that I enjoy, like pushing bulldogs into puddles or going to the beach to bark at ducks (don’t do it!). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try &lt;em&gt;MAZE DOG&lt;/em&gt; with a steamy cup of java this afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALEK</title>
      <link>p128.review/articles/dalek/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">p128.review/articles/dalek/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you play &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macintoshrepository.org/3230-classic-daleks&quot;&gt;DALEKS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, the old Mac game from the early nineties? It’s ok if you didn’t. In &lt;em&gt;DALEK&lt;/em&gt;, a faithful remake, you play as a lone stranger stuck on a huge grid with a bunch of Daleks (the weird villain race from Dr.Who). You can move your stranger in 8 directions and each time you move, the Daleks will move towards you. However, if two Daleks move to a space, they collide and crush each other. The goal of the game is to move your stranger so that all daleks die! EXTERMINATE THE EXTERMINATORS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game is quite tricky but charming. I just wish there were more variety as all levels play exactly the same.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Tavern Poker</title>
      <link>p128.review/articles/space-tavern-poker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">p128.review/articles/space-tavern-poker/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I suck at gambling. But I still find poker to be a fun pastime. In &lt;em&gt;Space Tavern Poker&lt;/em&gt; you’re stuck on a spaceport, low on space cash. You can take a seat at one of three tables (low, mid, high stakes) to play a hand or two of space poker. The AI-players have a tiny bit of personality, with different names and playing styles. Each player also has a spaceship that they will bet when they’re low on cash. Try to collect them all! Or, like me, sell your own ship so you can play a little more before you go bankrupt. If you want a light-hearted poker experience, you’ll like &lt;em&gt;Space Tavern Poker&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan Bee</title>
      <link>p128.review/articles/plan-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">p128.review/articles/plan-bee/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Plan Bee&lt;/em&gt; you play as a “bee”. A bee is a type of flying insect that plays a super important part of the eco-system. It “pollinates” the flowers by taking “pollen” from one flower to another, helping the flowers create new flowers, ensuring eco-diversity. It is your job as a player to navigate from flower to flower, collecting the pollen. But your bee is dizzy and starving, probably from &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colony_collapse_disorder&quot;&gt;colony collapse disorder&lt;/a&gt;, and will die soon should you fail to find new pollen in time or collapse to the ground! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plan Bee is a fun little 5 minute high-score single player game, sorta like Flappy Bird.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>